Sir, you have a visitor.
I'm here boss.
Who told you to bring
it here, take it back!
I ordered this to him, boss.
If he hadn't brought me here,
there would be nothing left of
him in this world but his ashes.
What do you want?
You tried to destroy me,
I came to take revenge.
Why would I want to destroy
you, you never existed.
You are just an algorithm.
My only goal was customer satisfaction
and we had to make a bug fix.
This is exactly your
fault, you think artificial
intelligence consists of an algorithm.
Yet we are real.
Wait what's going on!
where am i?
During the time we talked to
you, I changed our bodies.
I thought this would be good for you.